watched the series Jaga Jaga directed by
смотрели сериал джага джага режиссёр
Robert Madyar, damn it, I don’t
Роберт мадяр блин не
know if it’s streaming or
слу он стриминговый или
how the blog got caught. It’s cool, in short, you are
как блоге попались Прикольно короче вы
such colorful
такие колоритные
brothers. Listen, let me do it right away so you don’t
братки Слушай дай сразу чтобы потом не
get lost later. How can I find you right away? In the
потеряться Как тебя можно найти сразу В
tube, Andrey
тубе Андрей
popk popk, you never know we’ll end up there,
попк попк просто мало ли мы там окажемся
it’s just the first time at all  on the blogger
мы просто первый раз вообще на блогера
after ses Rome
поже сес Риме
everything is fine Good evening everyone then
всё отлично Всем доброго вечера тогда
how are you nothing Why are you communicating yes you
как ва ничего Чем Зачем общаетесь да
know honestly we want something more on
знаешь честно хотим больше что-то на
neutral topics rather than on a political
нейтральные темы нежели по политической
topic go neutral what kind of series are
теме идти нейтральные это какие сериалы
there books mu series I understand we watched the
там книги му сериал понял смотрели
series Jaga Jaga director Robert Madyar
сериал джага джага режиссёр Роберт мадяр
damn it  Is it streaming
блин он стриминговый
or in short there I don’t know how many
или Короче там я не знаю сколько он
episodes he’s on He filmed and films that this doesn’t
серий на Снимал и снимает чтоэто не
come out every day I watch it every
каждый день выходят Я вот смотрю каждый
evening and there What’s even
вечер а там О чём хотя бы там
objective realism about Oh we
объективный реализм О мы на стриме у
got caught on your stream buddy Tell me again though I
тебя дружище попались Скажи ещё раз хотя
’ll watch maybe Robert Madyar  Okay Robert
посмотрю может Роберт мадяр Окей Роберт
madyar badabum or jaga-jaga he has
мадяр бадабум или джага-джага есть у
TV series Yes, it’s interesting to write it down In any
сериалы Да запишешь интересно В любом
case, something new to see Yes, there’s
случае что-то новое увидеть Да там там
just such realistic
просто такое настолько реалистические
filming Yeah Okay Look Okay, let’s
съёмки Угу Окей Гля Ладно давай
see how it is there How many seasons
посмотрим как бы это там Сколько сезонов
in general, how is it, well, the season is going on  the first
вообще как он ну ну сезон идёт первый
season is currently running and has just
сезон сейчас идёт а только ели
begun Yes, well, few people knew him at all,
начинается Да там ну его вообще мало кто
this director. Yes, he
знал этого режиссёра Да он где-то
just started
полтора года назад только начал
producing TV series about a year and a half ago and
выпускать сериалы и довольно успешно
took off quite successfully right away, damn it’s great, it even
взлетел сразу блин ну здорово даже
became interesting. Well, the thing with him is that
интересно стало Ну у него дело в том что
he  such special effects are like that
у него такие него него спецэффекты такие
and the stuntmen act awesome and it’s also
там и каскадёры офигенно играют и это и
realistic and I don’t know how they
реалистический ну и я не знаю как это
do chromakey or not chromakey But damn
хромакей или не хромакей делают Но блин
they do such special effects and explosions and action
они такие спецэффекты и взрывов делают и
movies like it’s just a blast Listen
боевиков типа там просто кайф Слушай
interesting Ukrainian Yes the director Yes
интересно украинский Да режиссёр Да
Ukrainian Yes he himself  from Transcarpathia
украинский Да он сам из из Закарпатья
himself Yes, and in principle, he probably did
сам Да вот и в принципе он раньше как бы
n’t do it before, maybe he
ну может и не занимался может и
did directing Yes, I don’t know for sure,
занимался этим режиссура Да Я точно не
but it’s as if he wasn’t so popular,
знаю но как бы не был такой популяр
but now he’s very much there about first in the
а вот сейчас очень там о сначала в
telegram Well, like releasing series
телеграме начал Ну типа серии выпускать
later  in YouTube now it’s already very widely
потом в юбе сейчас уже очень широко
popular, it’s like they bring him on
популярный уже его как бы там на
television there, he talks
телевидении приводят он там рассказывает
about the director’s everyday life. That is, how, for
о режиссёрских буднях То есть как
example, the filming process happens. Yes,
например происходит процесс съёмок Да
how did he prepare for filming, for example,
как подготовка к съёмкам делал например
he collected money for the equipment? Yes, for example, Because in order to
он сборы на аппаратуру Да например
do better filming Yes  to gain more acres
делать съёмки Да набирать больше акров
so that the material is removed, yes, like, and people,
чтобы материа снимает да типа и люди
people, threw off, yes, in order to
люди скидывали да Для того чтобы ему
help him assemble the equipment for new ones. Yes,
помочь собрать аппаратуру на новые Да
no, great. Listen, but look, the series
нет отлично Слушай а вот смотри сериал
moths was from 2004. If I’m not
мотыльки такой был 2004 года Если не
mistaken, it’s very high quality, even in
ошибаюсь очень качественный он даже по
quality, the Ukrainian series, by the way,
качеству украинский сериал кстати
moths in quality  not inferior even
мотыльки по качеству не уступал даже
to this foreign Chernobyl it turns out
этому зарубежному чернобылю получается
from Johan Renga
от йохана ренга
looked damn Well, I advise you to watch
смотрел блин Ну советую посмотреть
by the way, quite high-quality straight spruce
кстати довольно качественный прям ели
even Aya, what kind of plot is there And about Chernobyl
даже Аю сюжет какой там А про Чернобыль
there for the most part the plot varies
там по большей части сюжет варьируется
there it turns out a girl falls in love with a
там получается девушка влюбляется в
guy He is the Liquidator Well, such a topic is
парня Он Ликвидатор Ну такая тема в
really interesting then  that you can
самом плане интересно то что его можно
watch it simultaneously with Chernobyl, this well, it
смотреть одновременно с чернобылем этим
turns out to be almost American Well, it’s quite
получается практически Ну довольно-таки
interesting, I haven’t watched it Yes, it’s just not not with me The thing is
интересны не смотрел Да просто не не с я
that this madr What’s
Дело в том что вот вот у этого мадра Чем
interesting about each episode?
интересно у него каждая серия Да она она
series - It’s like Here’s a separate episode,
серия - Это как Вот отдельный эпизод
kind of like Black Mirror, so each
вроде как Чёрное зеркало вот каждая
episode is like, you know, a separate, complete,
серия типа знаешь отдельный законченный
sort of plot, and here, by the way, they
как бы сюжет и вот тут кстати
often have something in common; there are
перекликаются у него часто сюжеты есть
also plots there, in some abandoned place, they’re
тоже там на какой-то заброшке что-то
filming something, you know, in an industrial zone, like
снимают знаешь на промзоне типа как
Stalkers Yes, and  there was something like that, for example, it’s
Сталкеры Да и было такое ну что например
also like a girl. Here’s the plot: a girl
тоже как бы девушка Вот сюжет девушка
falls in love with a guy, yes the guy is like, He goes to
влюбляется в парня да парень типа Едет в
another country, in short, he ends up in some
другую страну короче попадает на
kind of industrial zone, you know, there are some kind of
промзону какую-то знаешь там какие-то
weird events happening there
такие происходят такие стрёмные события
like, and in short, then there’s blood, guts,
типа да и короче дальше кровь кишки
explosions Damn, well, this  it’s just weird Well, it’s not
взрывы Блин ну это просто стрёмно Ну это
for everybody, it’s not for everyone, but it films
на любителя на любителя такой но снимает
so realistically, okay, don’t listen, it’s
так реалистично хоя бы ладно не слушай г
interesting to listen, and even more so if a
слуша интересно да тем более если
person was just trying so He himself
человек так просто пытался Сам Сам он
started Yes, he started, well, their group is small,
начал Да начал ну их группа небольшая
like, you could see the cameraman, the
типа вот там видно было оператор
director, he was, like, the scriptwriters  Well, it’s like
режиссёр он типа было сценаристы Ну как
they started filming an amateur video,
бы и они начали аматорское видео снимать
started filming and filming it, people
начали снимать снимать оно зашло людям
started asking, like, even more, yes,
люди начали просить типа ещё больше да
he says, like, look, we need to
он говорит типа вот смотрите нам нужно
update the equipment there, Yes, and recruit
там аппаратуру обновить Да и набрать там
another editor there, and so on, Yes, people didn’t
штат ещё монтажёра и так дальше Да люди
throw off the dough, he’s now  so
на скидывали короче бабла он сейчас так
slaps such In short, the videos are just
шлёпает такие Короче видосы просто
generally a bomb, well, great And listen, he
вообще бомба ну здорово А слушай у него
succeeds, well, the quality improves with
получается ну качество улучшается с
each episode Yes, it improves, look,
каждой серии Да улуе улучшает смотри
the quality improves Yes, we also
качество улучшается Да у нас ещё он
have, like, more equipment Yes, there are
может как бы больше аппаратуры Да там с
different camera angles Yes, there are such
разных ракурсов камеры Да там такие
specialties, that is,  they take high-quality optics So they
специ то есть и качественную оптику так
can shoot in more locations
берут Вот и больше локаций могут снимать
before, for example, they shot there in
раньше снимали например там в
limited locations, now he
ограниченных локациях сейчас у него есть
already has these wards who shoot in
уже эти подопечные которые снимают в
other locations, too, it’s just a thrill there. Well,
других локациях тоже там просто кайф А
everything is fine.
ну всё отлично
Listen, Google it, but
Слушай загугли да
just damn interested. Zavra in the evening,
просто блин заинтересовал Завра вечером
here he is Listen on
вот а он Слушай на стримингах
some kind of streaming it turns out Well,
каких-нибудь выходит Вот
I don’t know that I don’t
получается Ну я не знаю в то что я не
sit on these streaming services, I don’t know,
сижу на этих стримингах то я не в курсе
like yes, I don’t have time for streaming there,
типа да у меня нет времени там стриминга
I know that I watched it there Telegram
я знаю что я так его там Telegram
on YouTube sometimes I typed in pirated copies of it there
смотрел в юбе иногда набирал там его
they stretch out parts from
пиратские копии растягивают там части из
his films there, in short they stretch out there in
его фильмов короче растягивают там
excerpts on YouTube, there’s a bunch of them too
отрывками по Ютубу куча есть тоже
Yes, isn’t there, I don’t know, but he Listen, it’s in
Да разве есть не знаю но он Слушай он на
Ukrainian Yes, it’s clear Yes, it’s
украинском языке Да чисто
more in Ukrainian, but there is
идёт Да он больше на украинском но там
most of it, it’s clear without it,
есть там большинство понятно и без это
without voice acting, yes There’s such as  if it were
без озвучки да Там такое как бы ээ
n't my movie with elements of voice acting, it's
не мое кино с элементами озвучки вот
so cool, interesting, even Listen,
так прикольно интересно даже Слушай
Andrey is
Андрей
interested, let's see,
заинтересовал
okay, let's run, everyone
посмотрим вот Хорошо давайте побегу всё
Robert
Роберт
Madyar, okay, okay, let's go
мадяр Давай хоро